popstaronline.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy - POPSTAR!

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**             **This Privacy Policy governs each website, mobile site, application and/or other service, regardless of how distributed, transmitted, published or broadcast (herein collectively “Services”) provided by Popstar Publishing, Inc. (“Popstar,” “we,” “us,” or “our”).

**(1)   Information You Provide**

We may ask you to provide us with certain categories of information such as: (1) personal information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally, such as your name, e-mail address, date of birth and physical address (“Personal Information”); and (2) demographic information such as information about your family and age (“Demographic Information”).  We may collect this information through various places through the Services, including online subscription, contact us forms, or when you otherwise interact with us.

(a)  Cookies and Other Technology

A cookie is a data file that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computer and is stored on your computer or other device being used to access the Services.  Some cookies are Flash Cookies, which is a data file placed on your computer or other device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in or downloaded by you to your computer or device.  Cookies and Flash are standard in the industry and may be used for many purposes.  These keep track of things such as areas of the website you visit, for how long, and the websites that referred you to the website or applications, to track your preferences and interests.  If you choose to disable cookies or Flash cookies on your computer or device, some features of the Services may not function properly.

We may also use cookie information to collect aggregate information about web site users on an anonymous basis.  We may shore this aggregate demographic and usage information with our prospective and actual business partners, advertisers, and other third parties for any business purpose.

Some of our emails may contain tags that allow us and our advertisers and other partners to determine the type of content that may be of interest to you.  Those tags may contain Personally Identifiable Information and may be shared with others.  These tags may not be deleted but you can opt out of receiving theses emails.

(b)  IP Addresses

Your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer or device, usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet.  When you access our Services, we collect some general information about your computer or device, including its IP address, the operating system it uses, the browser software it uses, and your Internet service provider.  We may also retain information regarding the pages you visited, the web sites you visited after visiting this web site, the ads you see, and the ads you click on.  We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our services, gather broad demographic information, and administer our Services.

(c)  GIFS

We may use “clear GIFs” (aka “web becons” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies, in the sites and in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a web page or received a message.  A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well) located on a web page or in an e-mail or other type of message which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a web page or message.  We may use this technology, or similar technology, to assist us in delivering cookies on our online Services, to count users of the online Services, to monitor how users navigate the online Services, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or acted upon, or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

(d)  Embedded Scripts

An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interaction with the Services, such as the links you click on.  The code is temporarily downloaded onto your computer or device from our web server or a third-party service provider, is only active while you are connected to the Services, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

(e)  Third Parties

We may receive information from third parties, including Demographic Information from your mobile carrier, and information from third parties that solicit subscriptions to our magazines.

Also, if you choose to access, visit, and/or use any third party social networking service(s) that may be integrated with the Services, we may receive personally identifiable information and other information about you and your computer, mobile or other device that you have made available to those services, including information about your contacts on those services.  For example, some social networking services allow you to push content from our Services to your contacts or to pull information about your contacts so you can connect with them on or through our Service.  Some social networking services also will facilitate your registration for our Service or enhance or personalize your experience on our Services.  Your decision to use a social networking site in connection with our Services is voluntary.  However, you should make sure you are comfortable with the information your third party social networking services may make available to our Services by visiting those services’ privacy policies and/or modifying your privacy setting directly with those services’ privacy policies and/or modifying your privacy setting directly with those services.  We reserve the right to use, transfer, assign, sell, share, and provide access to all personally identifiable information and other information about you and your computer, mobile or other device that we receive through third-party social networking services in the same ways described in this Agreement as all of your other information.

(f)  Tracking Requests

Some third-party browsers provide “do not track” machine readable signals for websites or other online Services which are automatically applied by default and therefore do not necessarily reflect our visitors’ choice as to whether they wish to receive advertisements tailored to their interests.  As a result, we do not respond to these signals.  Go to [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) if you wish to learn more about your options to not accept tracking cookies for the purpose of receiving targeted interest-based advertisements.

**(2)   Use of Information**

(a)  We use information we collect from you in part to provide you with the service you have requested.  If you subscribe to POPSTAR, we may also use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your mailing address to send you your magazine.  Similarly, if you enter online sweepstakes, we will use this information to notify you if you are a winner.  We also use your information to identify you as a user, improve our Services, and send you administrative notifications, and respond to your inquiries.  We might also send out e-mails to users and sweepstakes/contest entrants to announce special offers, services and announcements.

(b) We may combine and use any and all information we collect on you either online or otherwise, including from third parties, for marketing purposes.

(c)  In addition, we may use the information you provide us through emails, Q&A, blogs, forums, in response to polls, or through any other user generated submission for editorial purposes, and may use your name and any stories you provide us in articles published online and in our magazine.  If you provide us with personal anecdotes, they may be attributed to you.  We can edit, rewrite, use and reuse the content, including your name, likeness, photograph, and biographical information you provide, with or without attribution, including publication in the magazine, and in trade media and advertising.

(e)  We may create Anonymous Information from Personally Identifiable Information by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you.  We use this Anonymous Information for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties in our sole discretion.

**(3)   Disclosure of Your Information**

(a)  We use Personal Information that you supply through the Services to provide you with the merchandise, product, service and/or content you have requested.

(b)  Unless otherwise specified on the Services, we may sell or share information about you and your computer, mobile or other device, including without limitation your Personal Information with carefully selected companies who we think may offer services and/or products that may be of interest to you.  In the event that you provide your email address in connection with a requested product or content, we may send you related commercial messages.  If you do not wish to receive future commercial messages from us, simply follow the unsubscribe instruction contained within the message you receive.  You may continue to receive certain communications from us, such as transactional or relationship message and/or messages about your account.

(c)  We may also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, market research, community forums management, auction services, and shopping, personal/job search and other classified ads functionality, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services, including without limitation content, on or through features on the Services, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card or other payment processing, order fulfillment, credit pre-authorization, and address verification.  There are also times when you provide information about yourself to us in areas of the Services that may be managed or participated in by third parties.  In such cases, the information may be used by us and by third party(ies) each pursuant to its own policies.  We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests.  While we may seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies.

(d)  Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, servicers and databases located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where privacy laws may not be as protective as your jurisdiction.  Please be advised that we may transfer your information from any state, province country or other governmental jurisdiction, and process it in the United States, or elsewhere.  Your content to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to such transfer.

(e)  We reserve the right to access, use and share with others your Personal Information for the purposes of health, safety and other matters in the public interest.

(f)  We may also provide access to our database in order to cooperate with official investigations or legal proceeding initiated by governmental and/or law enforcement officials, as well as private parties, including, for example, in response to subpoenas, search warrants, court orders, or other legal process.

(g)  In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, mobile or other device (including its geographic location), which at times may be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, analyze trends, track users’ movement around the Service, and to otherwise administer the Service.  Geographic location information about you and/or your computer, mobile or other device may specifically be used to show you content and sponsored messaging based on geographic location.

(h)  We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any lawful business purpose, such as analyzing trends and seeking compatible advertisers, sponsors, clients and customers.

(i)  In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets.  In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by us, our parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Service users may be among the transferred assets.

(j)  We reserve the right to identify you from your registration information and/or merge or co-mingle anonymous or non-personally identifiable data about you, your offline and online behavior, and/or your computer, mobile or other device (including its geographic location), with your Personal Information and/or other personally identifiable data for any lawful business purpose.

(j)  We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a “Promotion”) through the Services that may require registration for the Promotion.  By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, allowing the sponsor of the Promotions to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion.   If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s official rules, such as on a winners list.

**(4)   Your California Privacy Rights**

California’s “Shine the Light” law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the businesses’ practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.  Alternatively, such business may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information sharing.  Pursuant to the Shine the Light Law, Popstar will respond to written requests for this information.  If you would like to request this information, please send your written request to the contact address listed below.

**(5)   Policies for Individuals Under 13**

(a)  These Services are not intended for use by children, especially those under the age of 13.  No one under the age of 13 is allowed to register for the Service or provide any personally identifiable information to the Services.  Minors between the ages of 13 to 17, inclusive, must get permission from a parent or legal guardian before making purchases, including subscription, on this Service.

(b)  If a child discloses information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Service, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties.  Accordingly, parents or legal guardians should instruct children not to provide such information on this website, or the internet in general.

**(6)   Privacy Policy Coordinator and Other Privacy Inquiries**

**             **For all questions and concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

POPSTAR PUBLISHING, INC.

Attn: Privacy Policy Coordinator  
1810 East Sahara Ave. Suite 751

Las Vegas, NV 89104

**If you do not agree to the terms contained in this Privacy Policy and/or User Agreement, you must immediately exit the Services.**
